pcstats.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use - PCSTATS.com

**Privacy Policy and Terms of Use**

**Terms of Use:**  
All images, text, or other media contained on this website are the property of PCSTATS.com. Replication or duplication of the materials contained within PCSTATS.com Articles, website, including the PCSTATS.com logo are strictly forbidden without express _written_ permission. Please see PCSTATS.com's Terms of Use for more information.

**Web User Privacy Statement**

* * *

Rydium strongly believes in a consumer's right to privacy. All web user data collected by Rydium as part of the ad serving process is not personally identifiable (browser type, for example) and is used in aggregate form. Rydium does not conduct individual web user "profiling".

 **Cookies**  
Remote "cookies" on web user computers and server databases at Rydium facilities are used to store information by Rydium. A cookie is a piece of data placed on the Web User's hard drive by our servers. Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements. Cookies are not viruses and cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information.  
Cookies are used to ensure that when a web user clicks on an ad, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. They are also used by our reporting system to estimate the total reach of an ad campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to sequence the delivery of a series of ads to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement.Web Users have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in their browser. Please see your browser supplier's website for details on how to do this.

 **Information Collection and Use**  
As with all web content delivery systems, Rydium records information about the interaction between a web user's browser and our servers. Those interactions include ad content (banner) delivery, counting click-throughs on an ad, and tracking webpage views after a click-through. Browsers typically provide the browser version, the operating system, and the IP address of the computer in use. This non-personally identifiable information is collected from web users to assist in the proper function of our service as well as the targeting of advertisements from our customers and the reporting of aggregate data to both advertisers and publishers. Rydium does not collect, use, sell, or purchase web user information that is personally identifiable.

 **Information Sharing**  
Web user information (all of which is non-personally identifiable) is shared with our advertisers and publishers in aggregate fashion. This means, for example, that of the millions of web users we deliver banners to each month, an advertiser will know what percentage of those users viewed their advertisement with a certain browser. The sharing of this information is essential to providing the services we offer. Rydium may augment web user information with additional non-personally identifiable information, such as an IP address to 5-digit postal code cross reference to aid in local targeting of advertising. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information by Rydium.

 **Contacting Rydium**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, [contact us.](http://www.pcstats.com/feedback.cfm)

Ad choices

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, follow this link to the NAI universal user opt-out (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
